[
    {"question": "Cat", "answer": "Katt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Dog", "answer": "Hund","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "House", "answer": "Hus","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Car", "answer": "Bil","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Book", "answer": "Bok","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Pen", "answer": "Penna","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Table", "answer": "Bord","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Chair", "answer": "Stol","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Window", "answer": "Fönster","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Door", "answer": "Dörr","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Friend", "answer": "Vän","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Family", "answer": "Familj","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "School", "answer": "Skola","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Teacher", "answer": "Lärare","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Student", "answer": "Elev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Food", "answer": "Mat","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Water", "answer": "Vatten","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Coffee", "answer": "Kaffe","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Tea", "answer": "Te","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fruit", "answer": "Frukt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Vegetable", "answer": "Grönsak","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Bread", "answer": "Bröd","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Butter", "answer": "Smör","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Cheese", "answer": "Ost","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Milk", "answer": "Mjölk","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Meat", "answer": "Kött","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fish", "answer": "Fisk","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Egg", "answer": "Ägg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sugar", "answer": "Socker","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Salt", "answer": "Salt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Pepper", "answer": "Peppar","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Plate", "answer": "Tallrik","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Glass", "answer": "Glas","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Cup", "answer": "Kopp","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Spoon", "answer": "Sked","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fork", "answer": "Gaffel","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Knife", "answer": "Kniv","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Bed", "answer": "Säng","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Pillow", "answer": "Kudde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Blanket", "answer": "Täcke","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shower", "answer": "Dusch","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Bathtub", "answer": "Badkar","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Soap", "answer": "Tvål","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shampoo", "answer": "Schampo","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Towel", "answer": "Handduk","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Mirror", "answer": "Spegel","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Toothbrush", "answer": "Tandborste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Toothpaste", "answer": "Tandkräm","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Clothes", "answer": "Kläder","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shoes", "answer": "Skor","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Pants", "answer": "Byxor","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sweater", "answer": "Tröja","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Jacket", "answer": "Jacka","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Hat", "answer": "Hatt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Gloves", "answer": "Handskar","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Socks", "answer": "Strumpor","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shirt", "answer": "Skjorta","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Skirt", "answer": "Kjol","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Dress", "answer": "Klänning","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Underwear", "answer": "Underkläder","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Mobile phone", "answer": "Mobiltelefon","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Computer", "answer": "Dator","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Television", "answer": "TV","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Radio", "answer": "Radio","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Camera", "answer": "Kamera","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Watch", "answer": "Klocka","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Newspaper", "answer": "Tidning","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Letter", "answer": "Brev","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Mail", "answer": "Post","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Bank", "answer": "Bank","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Money", "answer": "Pengar","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Credit card", "answer": "Kreditkort","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Store", "answer": "Butik","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Market", "answer": "Marknad","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Restaurant", "answer": "Restaurang","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Cafe", "answer": "Kafé","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Hospital", "answer": "Sjukhus","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Pharmacy", "answer": "Apotek","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Doctor", "answer": "Läkare","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Nurse", "answer": "Sjuksköterska","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Police", "answer": "Polis","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Firefighter", "answer": "Brandman","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Bus", "answer": "Buss","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Train", "answer": "Tåg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Airplane", "answer": "Flygplan","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Boat", "answer": "Båt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Bicycle", "answer": "Cykel","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Taxi", "answer": "Taxi","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Road", "answer": "Väg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Street", "answer": "Gata","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Park", "answer": "Park","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Garden", "answer": "Trädgård","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Flower", "answer": "Blomma","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Tree", "answer": "Träd","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sea", "answer": "Hav","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "River", "answer": "Flod","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Mountain", "answer": "Berg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Forest", "answer": "Skog","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Run", "answer": "Springa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Is", "answer": "Är","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Beautiful", "answer": "Vacker","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Write", "answer": "Skriva","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Was", "answer": "Var","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Quickly", "answer": "Snabbt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Help", "answer": "Hjälpa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Become", "answer": "Blir","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Tall", "answer": "Lång","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Jump", "answer": "Hoppa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Are", "answer": "Är","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Carefully", "answer": "Försiktigt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Happy", "answer": "Glad","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Read", "answer": "Läsa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Been", "answer": "Varit","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Slowly", "answer": "Långsamt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Strong", "answer": "Stark","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Walk", "answer": "Gå","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Have", "answer": "Har","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Kind", "answer": "Snäll","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shout", "answer": "Skrika","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Will", "answer": "Kommer","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Quiet", "answer": "Tyst","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sit", "answer": "Sitta","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Would", "answer": "Skulle","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Brave", "answer": "Modig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Drive", "answer": "Köra","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Can", "answer": "Kan","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Angry", "answer": "Arg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fly", "answer": "Flyga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Must", "answer": "Måste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Tired", "answer": "Trött","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Swim", "answer": "Simma","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Should", "answer": "Borde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sad", "answer": "Ledsen","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fix", "answer": "Laga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "May", "answer": "Får","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Rich", "answer": "Rik","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Build", "answer": "Bygga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Want", "answer": "Vill","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Poor", "answer": "Fattig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Teach", "answer": "Lära","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Need", "answer": "Behöver","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Funny", "answer": "Rolig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Buy", "answer": "Köpa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shall", "answer": "Skall","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Calm", "answer": "Lugn","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sell", "answer": "Sälja","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Could", "answer": "Kunde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Friendly", "answer": "Vänlig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Speak", "answer": "Tala","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Would", "answer": "Skulle","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fast", "answer": "Snabb","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Listen", "answer": "Lyssna","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Ought", "answer": "Bör","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Weak", "answer": "Svag","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "See", "answer": "Se","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Must", "answer": "Måste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Short", "answer": "Kort","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Think", "answer": "Tänka","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "May", "answer": "Får","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Long", "answer": "Lång","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Feel", "answer": "Känna","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Want", "answer": "Vill","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Thick", "answer": "Tjock","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Write", "answer": "Skriva","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Need", "answer": "Behöver","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Thin", "answer": "Tunn","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Read", "answer": "Läsa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Can", "answer": "Kan","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "High", "answer": "Hög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Do", "answer": "Göra","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shall", "answer": "Skall","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Low", "answer": "Låg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Say", "answer": "Säga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Should", "answer": "Borde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Big", "answer": "Stor","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Go", "answer": "Gå","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Will", "answer": "Kommer","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Small", "answer": "Liten","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Come", "answer": "Komma","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Have", "answer": "Har","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "New", "answer": "Ny","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Eat", "answer": "Äta","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Been", "answer": "Varit","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Old", "answer": "Gammal","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Drink", "answer": "Dricka","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Is", "answer": "Är","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Warm", "answer": "Varm","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sleep", "answer": "Sova","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Was", "answer": "Var","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Cold", "answer": "Kall","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Wake", "answer": "Vakna","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Are", "answer": "Är","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Dry", "answer": "Torr","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Run", "answer": "Springa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Been", "answer": "Varit","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Wet", "answer": "Våt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shout", "answer": "Skrika","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Will", "answer": "Kommer","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Quiet", "answer": "Tyst","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sit", "answer": "Sitta","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Would", "answer": "Skulle","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Brave", "answer": "Modig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Drive", "answer": "Köra","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Can", "answer": "Kan","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Angry", "answer": "Arg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fly", "answer": "Flyga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Must", "answer": "Måste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Tired", "answer": "Trött","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Swim", "answer": "Simma","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Should", "answer": "Borde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sad", "answer": "Ledsen","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fix", "answer": "Laga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "May", "answer": "Får","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Rich", "answer": "Rik","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Build", "answer": "Bygga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Want", "answer": "Vill","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Poor", "answer": "Fattig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Teach", "answer": "Lära","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Need", "answer": "Behöver","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Funny", "answer": "Rolig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Buy", "answer": "Köpa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shall", "answer": "Skall","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Calm", "answer": "Lugn","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sell", "answer": "Sälja","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Could", "answer": "Kunde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Friendly", "answer": "Vänlig","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Speak", "answer": "Tala","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Would", "answer": "Skulle","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Fast", "answer": "Snabb","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Listen", "answer": "Lyssna","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Ought", "answer": "Bör","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Weak", "answer": "Svag","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "See", "answer": "Se","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Must", "answer": "Måste","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Short", "answer": "Kort","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Think", "answer": "Tänka","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "May", "answer": "Får","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Long", "answer": "Lång","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Feel", "answer": "Känna","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Want", "answer": "Vill","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Thick", "answer": "Tjock","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Write", "answer": "Skriva","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Need", "answer": "Behöver","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Thin", "answer": "Tunn","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Read", "answer": "Läsa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Can", "answer": "Kan","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "High", "answer": "Hög","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Do", "answer": "Göra","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Shall", "answer": "Skall","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Low", "answer": "Låg","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Say", "answer": "Säga","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Should", "answer": "Borde","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Big", "answer": "Stor","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Go", "answer": "Gå","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Will", "answer": "Kommer","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Small", "answer": "Liten","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Come", "answer": "Komma","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Have", "answer": "Har","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "New", "answer": "Ny","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Eat", "answer": "Äta","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Been", "answer": "Varit","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Old", "answer": "Gammal","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Drink", "answer": "Dricka","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Is", "answer": "Är","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Warm", "answer": "Varm","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Sleep", "answer": "Sova","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Was", "answer": "Var","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Cold", "answer": "Kall","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Wake", "answer": "Vakna","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Are", "answer": "Är","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Dry", "answer": "Torr","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Run", "answer": "Springa","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Been", "answer": "Varit","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"},
    {"question": "Wet", "answer": "Våt","question_language": "English", "answer_language": "Swedish"}
   ]